A Guide to the Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac Railroad Records, 1834-1997
Library of Virginia
- Series XIX: Richmond-Greyhound Lines, Inc., 1926-1971, n.d., 1 cubic foot and 1 volume. (Box 283-285)
  The Minute book covers the years 1932-1960 and includes Articles of Incorporation; the minute files for Board of Directors and Stockholders date 1951-1959; in addition there is a notice and some correspondence for 1968-1971, as well as Bylaws, 1935. The financial files, 1958-1968 concern mostly the stock exchange and proposed merger of Richmond Greyhound Lines into the Greyhound Corp., which sought to obtain the shares held by R.F. & P in 1958; there are statements, reports, and correspondence; also of Greyhound Corp. and Richmond Union Terminal Corp. They are arranged in alphabetical order. Also contains a brief history, 1926-1942, starting with the foundation of predecessor Richmond-Washington Motor Coaches.
  - XIX.A. General Administration, Management, 1932-1960, 1968-1971
    - Minutes Book, Board of Directors and Stockholders Meeting, 12 Nov 1932-9 Sep 1960, 1 vol. (Box 283)
      Do not serve original. Available on microfilm, Misc. Reel 2169.
    - Minute Files: Board of Directors, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 283:1)
    - Minutes Files: Board of Directors and Stockholders, 1953 (Box-folder 283:2)
    - Minutes Files: Board of Directors and Stockholders, 1953 (Box-folder 283:2)
    - Minutes Files: Board of Directors, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 283:3)
    - Minutes Files: Board of Directors and Stockholders, 1956 (Box-folder 283:4)
    - Minutes Files: Board of Directors, 1957 (Box-folder 283:5)
    - Minutes Files: Board of Directors, 1958 (Box-folder 283:6)
      Includes: Richmond Terminal Corp. and Greyhound Terminal of Washington meeting minutes.
    - Minutes Files: Board of Directors and Stockholders, 1959 (Box-folder 283:7)
      Includes: Greyhound Terminal of Washington meeting minutes.
    - Minutes Files: Annual Meeting Notices of The Greyhound Corp. and related correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 283:8)
  - XIX.B. Legal Department, ca. 1935
    - Bylaws, ca. 1935 (Box-folder 283:9)
  - XIX.C. Finance Department: Financial files (concern mostly the stock exchange and proposed merger of R.G. Lines into the Greyhound Corp., which sought to obtain the shares held by R.F. & P.; statements, reports, correspondence; also of Greyhound Corp. and Richmond Union Terminal Corp.), 1958-1968
    - Capital Expenditures, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 283:10)
    - Reports on Proposed Sale of R.F. & P. R.R. Interest in Richmond-Greyhound Lines, Inc., 1958, 2 copies (Box-folder 284:1-2)
    - Richmond Union Terminal Corporation, Financial Statements, 31 Oct 1959 (Box-folder 284:3)
    - Special Report to the Directors and Officers of the R.F. & P. R.R., prepared by The Greyhound Corporation, 1958, 2 copies, and correspondence (Box-folder 284:4)
    - Stock Tender, 30 Sep 1952-29 Dec 1958 (Box-folder 284:5-8)
    - Stock Tender, 2 Jan 1959-31 Dec 1960 (Box-folder 284:9-13)
    - Stock Tender, 17 Feb 1961-31 Dec 1962 (Box-folder 285:1-4)
    - Stock Tender, 1 Jan 1963-17 Jan 1964 (Box-folder 285:5-8)
    - Stock Tender, 17 Jan 1964-12 Oct 1965 (Box-folder 285:9-10)
  - XIX.D. Miscellaneous Files, 1926-1942, n.d.
    - Corporate history, 1926-1942, n.d. (Box-folder 285:11)
- Series XX: Richmond Holding Corp., 1957-1975, .225 cubic feet and 1 volume. (Box 286)
  The Minute book, 1957-1975 for this R.F.& P. subsidiary includes articles of incorporation, and minutes of the organization meeting, board of Directors and stockholders meetings; minute files cover 1961-1970 and include copies of meeting minutes, excerpts of minutes, and some financial information; Financial files, 1963-1976 contain check stubs and a real estate tax file. Some legal real estate files for this company can be found in Series II.D.
  Files in each subseries are arranged alphabetically and chronologically within each record type.
  - XX.A. General Administration, Management, 1957-1975
    - Minute Book, Feb 1957-Feb 1975 (Box 286)
      Includes: bylaws, articles of incorporation, and minutes of organization meeting.
      Do not serve original. Available on microfilm, Misc. Reel 2168.
    - Minute Files: Board of Directors and Stockholders, 1961 (Box-folder 286:1)
    - Minute Files: Board of Directors and Stockholders, 1962 (Box-folder 286:2)
    - Minute Files: Board of Directors and Stockholders, 1963 (Box-folder 286:3)
    - Minute Files: Board of Directors and Stockholders, 1964 (Box-folder 286:4)
    - Minute Files: Board of Directors and Stockholders, 1965 (Box-folder 286:5)
    - Minute Files: Board of Directors and Stockholders, 1966 (Box-folder 286:6)
    - Minute Files: Board of Directors and Stockholders, 1967 (Box-folder 286:7)
    - Minute Files: Board of Directors and Stockholders, 1968 (Box-folder 286:8)
    - Minute Files: Board of Directors and Stockholders, 1969 (Box-folder 286:9)
    - Minute Files: Board of Directors and Stockholders, 1970 (Box-folder 286:10)
  - XX.B. Finance Department, 1963-1975
    - Check stub, No. 101-352, First and Merchant's National Bank, 8 Feb 1963-9 Aug 1968 (Box-folder 286:11)
    - Check stubs, No. 353-604, First and Merchant's National Bank, 26 Aug 1968-12 Mar 1973 (Box-folder 286:12)
    - Check stubs, No. 605-759, First and Merchant's National Bank, 16 Mar 1973-4 Sep 1975 (Box-folder 286:13)
    - Real Estate Taxes, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 286:14)
- Series XXI: Richmond Land Corporation, 1915-1987, 1.4 cubic feet and 7 volumes. (Box 287-293)
  Founded in 1915. Included are minutes, 1915-1970 and financial records, 1915-1987 for this R.F.& P. subsidiary. Some legal real estate files for this company can be found in Series II.D. Included is a minute book, that covers the years 1915-1954; the minute files include copies of meeting minutes, excerpts of meeting and some financial data and cover the years, 1924-1970, but there are no minutes included for 1955-1961. The accounting and bookkeeping records, 1916-1974, include a balance, cashbooks, check stubs, journals and ledgers. There is one volume of stock certificates, 1915-1916, 1975, and real estate tax information for the years 1974-1987.
  - XXI.A. General Administration, Management, 1915-1954, 1961-1970
    - Minute Book No. 1, Dec 1915-Dec 1954, 1 vol.; Available on Misc. Reel 2171; Do not use original. (Box 287)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 21 Apr 1924 (Box-folder 287:1)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 30 Jun 1924 (Box-folder 287:2)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1 Nov 1924 (Box-folder 287:3)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 20 Apr 1924 (Box-folder 287:4)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 20 Apr 1925 (Box-folder 287:5)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 19 Apr 1924 (Box-folder 287:6)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 19 Apr 1926 (Box-folder 287:7)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 18 May 1926 (Box-folder 287:8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 5 Jan 1927 (Box-folder 287:9)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 18 Apr 1927 (Box-folder 287:10)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 13 May 1927 (Box-folder 287:11)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 20 Apr 1928 (Box-folder 287:12)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 16 Apr 1928 (Box-folder 287:13)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 8 Oct 1928 (Box-folder 287:14)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 23 Feb 1929 (Box-folder 287:15)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 15 Apr 1929 (Box-folder 287:16)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 15 Apr 1929 (Box-folder 287:17)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 14 Nov 1929 (Box-folder 287:18)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 28 Mar 1930 (Box-folder 287:19)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 21 Apr 1930 (Box-folder 287:20)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 21 Apr 1920 (Box-folder 287:21)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 28 Jul 1930 (Box-folder 287:22)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 31 Jan 1931 (Box-folder 287:23)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 23 Mar 1931 (Box-folder 287:24)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 20 Apr 1931 (Box-folder 287:25)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2 Jun 1931 (Box-folder 287:26)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 8 Jun 1931 (Box-folder 287:27)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 15 Jul 1931 (Box-folder 287:28)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 21 Sep 1931 (Box-folder 287:29)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 18 Apr 1932 (Box-folder 287:30)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 19 Apr 1932 (Box-folder 287:31)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 7 Mar 1933 (Box-folder 287:32)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 17 Apr 1933 (Box-folder 287:33)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 17 Apr 1933 (Box-folder 287:34)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 26 Jun 1933 (Box-folder 287:35)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 11 Dec 1933 (Box-folder 287:36)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 16 Apr 1934 (Box-folder 287:37)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 16 Apr 1934 (Box-folder 287:38)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 23 May 1934 (Box-folder 287:39)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 5 Apr 1935 (Box-folder 287:40)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 15 Apr 1935 (Box-folder 288:1)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 15 Apr 1935 (Box-folder 288:2)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1 Nov 1935 (Box-folder 288:3)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 20 Apr 1936 (Box-folder 288:4)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 20 Apr 1936 (Box-folder 288:5)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 19 Oct 1936 (Box-folder 288:6)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 29 Mar 1937 (Box-folder 288:7)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 19 Apr 1937 (Box-folder 288:8)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 19 Apr 1937 (Box-folder 288:9)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 4 Aug 1937 (Box-folder 288:10)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 22 Nov 1937 (Box-folder 288:11)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 18 Apr 1938 (Box-folder 288:12)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 18 Apr 1938 (Box-folder 288:13)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 9 Feb 1939 (Box-folder 288:14)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 17 Apr 1939 (Box-folder 288:15)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 17 Apr 1939 (Box-folder 288:16)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 15 Apr 1940 (Box-folder 288:17)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 15 Apr 1940 (Box-folder 288:18)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 21 Apr 1941 (Box-folder 288:19)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 21 Apr 1941 (Box-folder 288:20)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 23 Jun 1941 (Box-folder 288:21)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 20 Apr 1942 (Box-folder 288:22)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 20 Apr 1942 (Box-folder 288:23)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 7 Oct 1942 (Box-folder 288:24)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 19 Oct 1943 (Box-folder 288:25)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 19 Apr 1943 (Box-folder 288:26)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 25 Sep 1943 (Box-folder 288:27)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 22 Dec 1943 (Box-folder 288:28)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 11 Jan 1944 (Box-folder 288:29)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 17 Apr 1944 (Box-folder 288:30)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 17 Apr 1944 (Box-folder 288:31)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 6 Nov 1944 (Box-folder 288:32)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 16 Apr 1945 (Box-folder 288:33)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 16 Apr 1945 (Box-folder 288:34)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 15 Apr 1946 (Box-folder 288:35)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 15 Apr 1946 (Box-folder 288:36)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 14 Mar 1947 (Box-folder 288:37)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 21 Apr 1947 (Box-folder 288:38)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 21 Apr 1947 (Box-folder 288:39)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 8 Dec 1947 (Box-folder 288:40)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 19 Apr 1948 (Box-folder 288:41)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 19 Apr 1948 (Box-folder 288:42)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 8 Apr 1949 (Box-folder 288:43)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 19 Apr 1949 (Box-folder 288:44)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 17 Apr 1950 (Box-folder 288:45)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 17 Apr 1950 (Box-folder 288:46)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 5 Oct 1950 (Box-folder 288:47)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 30 Nov 1950 (Box-folder 288:48)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 16 Apr 1951 (Box-folder 288:49)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 16 Apr 1951 (Box-folder 288:50)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 25 May 1951 (Box-folder 288:51)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 18 Dec 1951 (Box-folder 288:52)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 21 Apr 1951 (Box-folder 288:53)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 19 May 1952 (Box-folder 289:1)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 30 Dec 1952 (Box-folder 289:3)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 20 Apr 1953 (Box-folder 289:4)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 20 Apr 1953 (Box-folder 289:5)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 26 Aug 1953 (Box-folder 289:6)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 10 Dec 1953 (Box-folder 289:7)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 19 Apr 1954 (Box-folder 289:8)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 19 Apr 1954 (Box-folder 289:9)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 5 May 1954 (Box-folder 289:10)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 21 Dec 1954 (Box-folder 289:11)
    - Board of Directors and Stockholders Meetings, 17 Apr 1961 (Box-folder 289:12)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 5 Jan 1962 (Box-folder 289:13)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 16 Apr 1962 (Box-folder 289:14)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 16 Apr 1962 (Box-folder 289:15)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2 Aug 1962 (Box-folder 289:16)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2 Jan 1963 (Box-folder 289:17)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 15 Apr 1963 (Box-folder 289:18)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 15 Apr 1963 (Box-folder 289:19)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 15 Apr 1963 (Box-folder 289:20)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 29 May 1963 (Box-folder 289:21)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2 Aug 1963 (Box-folder 289:22)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2 Oct 1963 (Box-folder 289:23)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 31 Mar 1964 (Box-folder 289:24)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 20 Apr 1964 (Box-folder 289:25)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 20 Apr 1964 (Box-folder 289:26)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1 Jun 1964 (Box-folder 289:27)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 9 Nov 1964 (Box-folder 289:28)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 19 Apr 1965 (Box-folder 289:29)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 19 Apr 1965 (Box-folder 289:30)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 20 Dec 1965 (Box-folder 289:31)
    - Borad of Directors Meeting, 16 Apr, 1 Jun 1966 (Box-folder 289:32)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 16 Apr 1966 (Box-folder 289:32)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1967 (15 Feb, 31 Mar, 13 Jun, 24 Sep) (Box-folder 289:33)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 17 Apr 1976 (Box-folder 289:33)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1968 (4 Jan, 25 Mar, 15 Apr, 9 Sep) (Box-folder 289:34)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 15 Apr 1968 (Box-folder 289:34)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1969 (17 Mar, 21 Apr, 26 Aug, 13 Oct) (Box-folder 289:35)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 21 Apr 1969 (Box-folder 289:35)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1970 (16 Jan, 8 Apr, 8 Jul, 30 Oct) (Box-folder 289:36)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 20 Apr 1970 (Box-folder 289:36)
  - XXI.B. Finance Department, 1915-1987
    - XXI.B.1. Accounting and Bookkeeping
      - Balance: Trial Balance, Mar 1960-Mar 1963, 1 vol. (Box 290)
      - Cash Book/Vouchers, Jan 1921-Dec 1935, 1 vol. (Box 291)
      - Cash Book, Jan 1956-Jan 1963, 1 vol. (Box 291)
      - Check stubs No. 101-352, First & Merchants National Bank, 8 Feb 1963-15 Sep 1972 (Box-folder 291:1)
      - Check stubs No. 1-252, Central National Bank, 14 May 1964-11 Jul 1969 (Box-folder 291:2)
      - Check stubs No. 253-501, Central National Bank, 23 Jul 1969-18 Jan 1974 (Box-folder 291:3)
      - Journal (started in 1920; earlier entries retrospective), 1916-Dec 1929, 1 vol. (Box 291)
      - Ledger, Dec 1916-Dec 1937, 1 vol. (Box 292)
      - General Ledger, Jan 1934-Jan 1944, 1 vol. (Box 292)
      - General Ledger, Jan 1945, 1 vol. (Box 292)
    - XXI.B.2. Securities, 1915-1916, 1975
      - Stock certificates 1-98; Certificates 1-3 have been issued, 1915-1916, 1975, 1 vol. (Box 292)
    - XXI.B.3. Taxes, 1974-1987
      - Real Estate Taxes, 1974 (Box-folder 293:1)
      - Real Estate Taxes, 1976 (Box-folder 293:2)
      - Real Estate Taxes, 1982 (Box-folder 293:3)
      - Real Estate Taxes, 1983 (Box-folder 293:4)
      - Real Estate Taxes, 1984 (Box-folder 293:5)
      - Real Estate Taxes, 1985 (Box-folder 293:6-7)
      - Real Estate Taxes, 1986 (Box-folder 293:8-9)
      - Real Estate Taxes, 1987 (Box-folder 293:10)
- Series XXII: Richmond Terminal Railway Co., 1916-1975, .95 cubic feet and 20 volumes. (Box 294-312)
  Chartered in 1916 and dissolved in 1976. Included are Minutes, Legal Records, and Financial Records. The set of two minute books, 1916-1975 includes Articles of Incorporation and Board of Directors and Stockholders meeting minutes; the files, 1961-1970 include balance sheets, resolution and excerpts from minutes. Legal documents, 1922-1958 consist of Articles of Association, Charter and Bylaws (in chronological order), and miscellaneous contracts, 1922-1958. Financial records, 1916-1975, contain some accounting and bookkeeping records such as annual reports, journals and ledgers; stock certificates and first mortgage 5% gold bonds, as well as state tax returns for 1935-1950.
  - XXII.A. Minutes, 1916-1975
    Minutes files include balance sheets, some annual reports, correspondence and resolutions, and excerpts from the minutes.
    - Minute Book (Board of Directors and Stockholders), Aug 1916-Jun 1967, 1 vol. (Box 294)
      Do not serve original. Available on microfilm, Misc. Reel 2172.
    - Board of Directors Meeting, Mar 1961 (Box-folder 296:1)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 17 Apr 1961 (Box-folder 296:1)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 15 Mar 1962 (Box-folder 296:2)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 16 Apr 1962 (Box-folder 296:2)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 15 Mar 1963 (Box-folder 296:3)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 15 Apr 1963 (Box-folder 296:3)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 23 Mar 1964 (Box-folder 296:4)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 20 Apr 1964 (Box-folder 296:4)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 12 Apr, 19 Aug 1965 (Box-folder 296:5)
    - Stockholders Annual Meeting, 19 Apr 1965 (Box-folder 296:5)
    - Stockholders Special Meeting, 10 Jun 1965 (Box-folder 296:5)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 11 Apr 1966 (Box-folder 296:6)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 10 Apr 1967 (Box-folder 296:7)
    - Stockholders Meeting, 17 Apr 1967 (Box-folder 296:7)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 15 Apr 1968 (Box-folder 296:8)
    - Stockholders Meeting, 15 Apr 1968 (Box-folder 296:8)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 7 Apr 1969 (Box-folder 296:9)
    - Stockholders Meeting, 21 Apr 1969 (Box-folder 296:9)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 8 Apr 1970 (Box-folder 296:10)
    - Stockholders Meeting, 21 Apr 1970 (Box-folder 296:10)
  - XXII.B. Legal Department, 1916-1958
    - XXII.B.1. Charter and Bylaws, 1916, [192- ]
      - Articles of Association [Charter] (certified copy), 17 May 1916 (Box-folder 297:1)
      - Charter, 17 May 1916 (Box-folder 297:2)
      - Bylaws, [192- ], 2 copies (Box-folder 297:3)
    - XXII.B.2. Miscellaneous Contracts, 1922-1958
      - Agreement for Joint Use of Passenger Terminals; Annotated by Resolution, 1 Jan 1922 {15 Apr 1935] (Box-folder 297:4)
      - Agreement, 30 Apr 1958 (Box-folder 297:5)
      - Charter, First Mortgage, Operating Agreement and Miscellaneous Documents in Connection herewith, 1916-1922, 1 vol.; 2 copies (Box 297)
        One copy labeled "Eppa Hunton, Jr., President"
      - First Mortgage September 1, 1940 [Charter, 1916, and Bylaws], 1 vol. (Box 297)
        Included: copies of Charter, 1916, Bylaws, First Mortgage, Agreement, Memorandum of closing, Application to the Interstate Commerce commission, with accompanying papers and specimen of bonds; indexed.
      - First Mortgage September 1, 1940, 1 vol.; 2 copies (Box 298)
        Included: copies of First Mortgage, Agreement, Memorandum of closing, Application to the Interstate Commerce commission, with accomanying papers and specimen of bonds; indexed
  - XXII.C. Finance Department, 1916-1975
    Includes: 1. Accounting; 2. Securities; 3. Taxes (see also R.F. & P. R.R. Register of Authorities for Expenditures, 1919-1990
    - XXII.C.1. Accounting and Bookkeeping, 1924-1975
      - Annual Reports, 1924-1933 (Box-folder 299:1)
      - Annual Reports, 1934-42 (Box-folder 299:2)
      - Annual Reports, 1943-1950 (Box-folder 299:3)
      - Annual Reports, 1951-1954; 1955-1956, 2 copies each (Box-folder 299:4)
      - Annual Reports, 1957-1960, 2 copies each (Box-folder 299:5)
      - Annual Reports, 1961-1964, 2 copies each (Box-folder 299:6)
      - Annual Reports, 1965-1967, 2 copies each (Box-folder 299:7)
      - Annual Reports, 1968-1972, 2 copies each (Box-folder 299:8)
      - Annual Reports, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 299:9)
      - Journal No. 1, 31 Oct 1916-31 Dec 1922, 1 vol. (Othertype on shelf)
      - Journal No. 2, 31 Jan 1923-31 Dec 1926, 1 vol. (Othertype on shelf)
      - Journal No. 3, 31 Jan 1927-31 Dec 1929, 1 vol. (Box 300)
      - Journal No. 4, 31 Jan 1930-31 Dec 1937 (Othertype on shelf)
      - Journal No. 6, 31 Jan 1944-31 Dec 1948 (Othertype on shelf)
      - Journal No. 7, 31 Jan 1949-31 Dec 1953, 1 vol. (Box 301)
      - Journal No. 8, 31 Jan 1954-31 Dec 1958 (Othertype on shelf)
      - Journal No. 9, 1959-1962 (Box 302)
      - Journal No. 10, 1963-1965 (Box 303)
      - Journal No. 11, 1966-1969 (Box 304)
      - Journal, 1958 [sic], Jan 1970-Jul 1974 (Box 305)
      - Ledger No. 1, 1916-1923 (Othertype on shelf)
      - Ledger No. 2, 1923-1926 (Othertype on shelf)
      - Ledger No. 3, 1927-1930 (Othertype on shelf)
      - Ledger No. 4, 1930-1938 (Othertype on shelf)
      - Ledger No. 5, 1938-1944, 1 vol. (Box 306)
      - Ledger No. 6, 1944-1948, 1 vol. (Box 306)
      - Ledger No. 7, 1949-1953, 1 vol. (Box 307)
      - Ledger No. 8, 1954-1958, 1 vol. (Box 307)
      - Reconciliation Book, 1937-1964, 1 vol. (Box 308)
    - XXII.C.2. Securities, 1922-1976
      - Stock Certificates, Cancelled, 1959, 1974, 1 vol. (Box 309)
        Includes letter, 12 May 1976.
      - Transfers, First Mortgage, 5% Gold Bonds, 5 Jun 1922-20 Mar 1963, 1 vol. (Box-folder 310:1-3)
        Some Inserts were removed from volume and are filed in three file folders in same box.
    - XXII.C.3. Taxes, 1935-1950
      - State Tax Returns, 1935-1937 (Box-folder 311:1)
      - State Tax Returns, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 311:2)
      - State Tax Returns, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 311:3)
      - State Tax Returns, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 311:4)
      - State Tax Returns, 1944 (Box-folder 311:5)
      - State Tax Returns, 1945 (Box-folder 312:1)
      - State Tax Returns, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 312:2)
      - State Tax Returns, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 312:3)
      - State Tax Returns, 1950 (Box-folder 312:4)
- Series XXIII: Richmond Union Terminal Corporation, 1929-1960, 1 volume. (Box 312a)
  Chartered on 1 March 1929.
  - Minutes Book, Board of Directors and Stockholders, 21 Mar 1929-18 May 1960 (Box 312a)
    Minute book includes Board of Directors and Stockholders meeting minutes, certificate of incorporation, and bylaws.
    Do not serve original. Available on microfilm, Misc. Reel 2175.
- Series XXIV: Richmond-Washington Co., 1901-1971, .47 cubic feet and 1 volume. (Box 313-314)